

# Boian Ivanov Curriculum Vitæ

 Address:
 Lyulin 301, 1336 Sofia

 Phone:
 + 359 (0)878448744

 Born:
 27.05.1995

 Nationality:
 Bulgarian, Greek

Mail: boian.ivanov44@gmail.com
GitHub: github.com/boian-ivanov/
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/BoianIvanov/

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a Web Developer with experience in client-side and server-side technologies, mainly PHP and JavaScript. Currently working on the OpenCart platform, but that doesn't stop me from being interested in other programming methods. Always researching and developing something on the side, while working. Still my passion for my work is what drives me forward in life.

### WORK EXPERIENCE (Reference on demand)

#### Sapir Bulgaria LTD sapirshop.com

Present

Sofia, Bulgaria

Development and administration of e-commerce marketplace based on OpenCart. Module development on the platform.

#### IT STEP Computer Academy itstep.bg

2016 - 2017

Sofia, Bulgaria

Computer Science Educator - Composing and teaching courses in software education.

RS Consult *rsc.bg* 2016 - 2017

Sofia, Bulgaria

Web developer working with PHP, Laravel and OpenCart.

#### ITR Services itrservices.eu

2016

Sofia, Bulgaria

Web Development Intern. E-commerce development with Magento.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Computer Science and Informatics

2013-2017

New Bulgarian University, Sofia

• On-going education in the field of Informatics with focus on Object oriented programming, Web-Programming and Advanced Mathematics

# Maintenance of computer systems, applications and networks $\it Serres,\ Greece$

2011 - 2013

• Basic knowledge in networking and programming

## **LANGUAGES**

Bulgarian (mother tongue), Greek (fluent), English (fluent), German (B1)

## **OTHER QUALIFICATIONS**

Drivers license

2015

 $Sofia,\ Bulgaria$ 

Car (B,B1) and Motorbike(AM)